Coupe is the freaking bane of my
existence, man. I freaking hate coupe.
Stops all your bugs. Coupe is like one
of the worst things that for an attacker
that has ever happened to browser
security.
Best part of hacking when you can just,
you know, critical thing, right?
Yeah, dude.
[Music]
So when you're running an enterprise
security program, there are quite a few
things you need to nail before you even
consider doing something like running a
bug bounting program, right? The these
are kind of like the ABCs of enterprise
security. Um obviously you need some
sort of fishing prevention system. You
need an EDR. You need some um
introspection into your environment with
logging. And of course, you need some
sort of patch management system to make
sure that your software is constantly up
to date. And not going to lie, guys,
that last one is a little bit of a pain
in the butt, right? I know you guys know
what I'm talking about with that. It's
it's a lot. And whenever there is
something that's a pain in the butt in
security, what happens? Well, Threat
Locker always comes up with an
innovative solution. And that's exactly
what they've done with Threat Locker
patch management. Their team is working
constantly to ensure the software
updates for software in your ecosystem
are audited, categorized. So if there's
like a super severe zero day, you'll
definitely know about it. And then check
for conflicts with other software on
your system before enabling the
enterprise admin to automatically update
or schedule an update in the future. And
I'll just read this little snippet from
their website really quick, which I
loved. It says, "We'll even dare to say
install threat locker patch management
and forget about patch management. We've
got it covered."
That is what you love to hear. That is
what you love to hear, right? Okay. So,
definitely check it out, guys.
threatlocker.com/platform-management
or just go to threadlocker.com and uh
and look for the patch management
software. All right, that's a wrap.
Let's go back to the show.
Subhackers, really quick this week in
bug bounty segment for you. And for
those of you that don't remember, the
this week in bug bounty segment is where
we give you updates from the platforms
and other parts of the bug bounty
community. uh just sort of rapidfire
news section. Um and so this one we've
got Yes, We Hack is going to Let Hack
2025 and they're running a uh cool
competition I thought I'd shout out uh
called Payload. And this is going to be
essentially a polygot competition where
you create a payload that exploits XSS,
SQLI, command injection, derialization
bugs, and a couple other things. Uh this
is run by our boy BitK who we love who
did an amazing um uh master class for us
in the critical thinkers discord. Um
definitely want to get him on the pod at
some point but the output of his
research is unbelievable. I have so many
pages uh bookmarked from his research
and and tooling. Um so definitely shout
out to our boy Bid K. And if you guys
want to compete in this, go for it. Uh
June 27th 9:00 a.m. CST to June 28th 6
p.m. CST. Um,
and if you don't participate in it, it's
going to be really good to read the
writeups anyway because knowing all the
tips and tricks you can use to like
craft a payload in a really restricted
character set environment uh or whatever
really restrictive environment is a
super helpful skill for hackers to have.
So check it out. Um, payload please
competition at leak 2025 um and virtual.
All right, let's go back to the show.
Dude, let me tell you, man. Today is one
of those days where I just didn't really
want to come record a podcast. Like,
like, you know, and I'm excited because
we've got good content, but I was like
right in the middle of hacking something
when we scheduled this episode. But you
got derailed into something else where
you learned something pretty cool that
we'll talk about in this episode. Yeah.
All right. Well, let's let's jump right
into that. Okay. So, um yeah, thanks.
Let me let me restore my hype for for
this as well. um switch context a little
bit. So earlier today when we were
prepping for this episode um I you know
was going through the research as I do
by by Swanzer uh who recently released a
article called uh make self XSS great
again and um there was yeah right and
and there was a ton of really um useful
takeaways. We talked about credentialist
iframes on the on the pod before in
here, but those those are definitely a
big deal um in this environment. Uh and
the way that he you know the main
takeaway from the credentialist iframe
piece was that uh credentialist iframes
and iframes just normal iframes are are
same origin. So what that means is that
you can have two iframes embedded on the
page and you see him doing this right
here where one is logged in you know as
your victim. This is just a normal
iframe and and one is uh has no
credentials on it and yet these two
iframes are same origin. So this guy,
this unauthenticated dude can reach into
the authenticated iframe and grab, you
know, data out, which is super whack.
Yeah, super weird. Like it almost feels
like it's a browser bug. Yeah, it it
really does. Um and it says here,
looking at the RFC, we can see that
credentialist iframes are same or origin
as regular iframes. Um, and let's see
what he says here. I haven't actually
read that. It's it's mentioned that uh
implementing opaque origin similar to
sandbox domains wasn't implemented due
to implementation difficulties. Right?
So they they weren't able to make it not
same origin or have some sort of tweak
on same origin. Um, so they just made it
same origin which is really helpful. Um,
and what this essentially does, Joseph,
is it eliminates the need for a logout
curf in these sort of environments
because we can just drop our login curve
inside of a credentialist iframe and we
get a whole new cookie jar in that
iframe. That's right. You just reach in
there and Yep. and then use it. Yep.
Yep. So, you reach across and then grab.
Um, so the credentialist thing is is
super cool. Um, and there's a couple
other tips in this one that uh I wanted
to highlight as well. Um,
this one was just super cool right here.
This is self XSS plus CSUF with login uh
via with capta on login with capture.
Okay. And this is kind of a pain in the
butt thing where sometimes they've got a
capture, right? But I love that his
solution here is just so elegant, which
is it just opens up a web socket to the
attacker's, you know, page and just
pipes through the the capture. You just
wait. You wait for the victim to open
the page and then when they do, you type
in a capture. You solve it really quick
and then it triggers the sea surf,
right? Um it's almost like in the same
way you can do pass through when you're
fishing for like SMS. Yeah. Yeah.
Exactly. Um, so and like conceptually I
knew that this was possible, right? But
then if you see his like 10 lines of
code here that do it, I'm like, ah, this
is good. This is exactly what we want.
Why why is that? I feel like um not to
take us down a tiny rabbit hole here,
but I feel like there are so many times
when hacking um and also when doing
development work when for some reason
our brains are like, "Oh, this is just
like some difficult opaque blob of um of
a problem that I need to solve, but like
it's just too big for me to currently
solve or something." Or maybe you don't
even think that deep. It's just you just
think of this as like an unsolved
problem when really it's like very often
whenever you go to do it, it's like easy
or it only takes 10 minutes. kind of the
same way you let to-dos hang over your
life that you could just knock out in
five minutes instead of just knocking
them out, you know. Absolutely. And this
is especially true with AI now because
you can just say, "Hey, build a, you
know, websocket server that works like
this." And it just goes, you don't even
have to type out all the lines, right?
Um, so it was cool to see him implement
there that here to get around captions.
I would love to see somebody go and take
this research and build a framework for
this for recapture.
uh because recapture is not this simple.
So um I I think that it it would be
really cool to have some you know
framework where connects back to the
attacker's you know server or whatever
the attacker solves the capture and then
it gets all of those like sub requests
and stuff like that that are necessary
for uh recapture to go ahead and push
the request through. Yeah. Um that'd be
sick. Okay, now I'm going to skip the
the clickjacking one because I didn't
love that one. And we're going to move
on to this new um piece that he mentions
which utilizes this function called
fetch later. Okay. And this was a new uh
function that got added to um Chrome I
believe uh very recently. Um and
essentially what this allows it to do is
issue a fetch request with a certain
timeout on it. Um and that will uh what
Sansza was saying in this write up and
there was a little bit of controversy
about this on the on the CTV discord of
like ah does this work does this not
work? Yeah. Um but but what it does is
is later after that timeout it will send
the request with your current
authenticated session. And so Slunzer
was like okay well after we leave the
page you can still do this. Um, and it's
not exactly that simple, unfortunately,
because when you leave the page,
according to the MDN docs, uh, it it
actually, um, sends all of your your
fetch layers at the same time. Um, which
is kind of a pain in the butt. Uh, but
this does that include even if you like
kill the tab? Yeah. Yeah. If you close
that, I tested that. So, if you close
all of Chrome Yeah. completely, then uh,
it shoots it out real quick. just shoots
all the fetch letters at the last
second. Yeah, at the last second. It's
kind of weird. It is kind of weird. But
here's the the the crazier piece of this
was like, okay, well, how Slunzer wanted
to use it in a specific writeup was he
wanted to say, okay, you know, register
these fetch leaders and then wait, you
know, log the attacker out and then wait
for the victim to log in later and then
when it does, these fetch leaders will
will trigger and then, you know, it'll
run the attacker's request that they
wanted to run like, you know, give
whatever person admin rights or
whatever. Mh. Um,
however, it doesn't do that because if
you close the tab, it it just runs them
all right away. So, I was like, ah, how
can we get around this? And the solution
that I came up with was actually what
you do is you make a request to your own
server and you set the timeout super
long and you h you stall the HTTP
response from your own server uh for the
maximum amount of time that Chrome can
handle it, which is like 300 seconds.
Okay? And then you do that in a redirect
loop 20 times. So you can get you can
get up to an hour and a half. Okay. So
wait wait wait wait. We're gonna clarify
this. One, this isn't in the blog post.
You found this and thought of this. This
is my research, right? And and two, this
feels novel. Like this feels like
something no one's really thought about.
It's like a a massive feature to combine
with fetch later to enable an entire
attack. And I and I I I tried doing it
with fetch, too. I was like, um, you
know, maybe this isn't a fetch later
thing in particular. Maybe fetch can do
it too, but fetch will just stop if the
page has already been closed. Fetch
later has some like background async
properties that are going on with it
where it's not, you know, it like caches
whatever origin this was supposed to be
like living on when the the fetch later
request was issued. Wow. And it
continues, you know, you can continue
doing redirect after redirect after
redirect after redirect with these, you
know, maximum Chrome timeouts. And you
can uh extend that request uh all the
way up to an hour and a half. Is it is
it is it 30 redirects at 300 seconds
each? 20 redirects at 300 seconds each.
Yeah. So it's like a little over an hour
and a half um that you can do with that.
Uh and which is like not forever, but I
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And and uh and so I
think that there's still some viability
to this sort of delay piece of that
attack. M um and I guess also it's worth
mentioning that uh you know you need to
like 307 probably uh with this because
if you're going to be using a a post
request or whatever Yeah. then you'll
need to 307. Um but yeah, so I thought
that was an interesting piece that you
can continue to trigger these. That's
super cool. Yeah, that's amazing. So it
makes me wonder like uh anytime that I
hear anything about this, my mind
immediately jumps to what are the other
implications of this, right? Like I
wonder what other things this enables.
Like one thing that jumped to my mind is
uh attack like a user would often
probably log back in and want to reoff
pretty quickly if they're actively in
their browser which they're often going
to be in their browser if they get
seured because they're going to end up
on either a water hole attack or
something like that, right? So, so for
the initial thing to occur, they're
probably in their browser and then I
think an hour and a half is totally
actually reasonable for the attack to
occur because they might hop back to the
other tab, see they're logged out, log
back in. You know what I mean? It
doesn't actually feel unrealistic at
all. No. Yeah. And and I think a lot of
people will just, you know, you could
even just trigger a redirect to that
page and be like, "Oh, no. You're logged
out. What happened?" Yeah, that's a good
point. Yeah. Yeah. So, um it's tricky
though because you've only got
I guess you've only well you could
register a lot of uh yeah you could
register a lot of fetch later requests
and so you could do it at certain
increments as well just like you said in
the blog post. Okay. And then it works
man. It works. It does. Yeah. It's neat.
So I I'm excited. I've only you know uh
pocked it out a little bit but uh I
think this fetch later thing is super
weird and definitely should be the
subject of more research. So just as
like a super applicable way to to um
wrap this up with a bow one for people
like me who aren't doing a lot of
frontend stuff. So this is basically
when you have self accesss
and you have a login curve
and does is that it or do you also need
a credential iframe? No. So so you can
you can uh selfexs right. So you you get
the self XSS you you login curve it your
attacker into this you can do this
either via the credential iframe or you
can if you can find some way to get rid
of the current person session sometimes
login curve itself you know gets rid of
the current victim session um however
way you do that you could do it quick
jar overflow you could do it with you
know credentials iframes whatever and
then trigger the selfss and then
register these these fetch later
handlers right and then log the the
attacker Y and then these fetchers will
keep churning churning churning churn.
If they log in at all then it becomes a
stored XSS. Exactly. Then you can
trigger a fetch um to a specific And
it's interesting because it doesn't
necessarily trigger a It doesn't trigger
a stored XSS. It allows you to send a
fetch request. So you also need one more
gadget here. I'm glad you clarified this
uh Joseph. M you you also need you know
a oneshot fetch request that you can
issue that will you know affect the
victim's account in some negative way
you know change their password change
their email something like that right um
but but you're making it with their
credentials so you're making and it can
be a post request it doesn't have to be
it's not like a get based and it's same
origin and and it could actually be JSON
it doesn't even have to be it's not like
a postbased CSR it's literally any any
fetch request you can make with their
creds on their origin. So, it's probably
not that difficult, but you do have to
have something that like doesn't require
2FA or something unique. Yeah. Yeah. Or
the or like a Curf token or something,
right? Like the Well, even the Curf
token, no, because it would be coming
from the attacker's account. So, um
yeah, you would need you need to not
have anything in the request body that
you can't predict. Um so everything
would have to be done completely via
cookies, which you know, it's not that
rare. So, I think it's still a great
gadget still. Yeah. Oh, so it can't
actually it can't use a bear token
either.
Um, no it can't because the be the the
authentication that's happening here the
O boundary is like oh it's coming from
you know this same site right which is
what we did from the attackers you know
attacker session so if it was if it was
using you know anything besides cookies
then that obear is going to be different
on the victim session. Okay. So it has
to be cookies. Cool. See this is why we
need a uh a noob here to ask questions
to clarify the exact uh parameters by
which it's actually vulnerable. Yeah.
It's it's good either way, man. I mean,
like a lot of times we we get fixated on
these little pieces of gadgets, you
know, where we're like, oh, you know, I
just found a way to get persistence in
the browser, which is what this is,
right? This is a persistence in the
browser mechanism and then you kind of,
you know, until you build out the full
pock until you try to use it in
exploitation scenario, you're like, oh,
oh, I don't have delivery or oh, I don't
have impact, you know, or whatever.
Yeah, functions a little bit weirder.
So, yeah. All right, man. Uh, that's
that's all I had on this. Shout out to
Salonzer. Great research, man. Uh thanks
for bringing fetch later and
credentialist iframes shedding a little
bit more light on those. Speaking of
redirects, um we have some awesome
research from Shubs and asset
note/nowouse search light cyber as they
did another sweet blog post.
Yeah, dude. This thing is awesome. I I
can't believe that they actually found
some research that affects blind SSRFs
here because for a while everyone was
like, "Huh, that's of course that's an
amazing piece of research to go after,
but there's just never going to be any
way to do it, right?" Like it all is so
different. There probably is some impact
for some companies where they have like
some sort of internal internet site that
has like a git based, you know, endpoint
where you could do something state
changing, but without like white box
testing there, there's just nothing you
can usually find. Yeah. Yeah. But this
is this turns the blind SSRF into a full
SSRF in some scenarios. Um, and it's
super whack the way that they've dealt
with this. So, do you want to do you
want to give it the rundown on it or
should I? Yeah, sure. Um, I think you
got two more up. So, yeah, I'll do it.
Okay. Basically, they found um a
wow, an app, couldn't think of a good
word for it. An app where if they where
they found a blind SSRF and if they did
one or more or just, you know, one or a
few um redirects, it would give an
exception for invalid JSON. M um so
presumably, you know, it was trying to
parse that and respond with it or it was
trying to respond with JSON or maybe
there was like a secondary hop in there
that that um expected JSON, but because
it got an error message or something,
you know, it didn't actually properly
validate it. But then they noticed that
if they gave it 30 redirects or more, it
would actually fail with a network
exception and there would the invalid
JSON error went away. And so this
triggered in their mind like the idea
that oh wow there's like this isn't a
single endpoint. It's actually something
deeper. There's like a secondary
secondary context or maybe a third
context, right? And so they tested all
the different status codes and stuff and
they realized that if it if there was a
500 uh error HTTP status code, then it
would be a full uh HTTP response. The
sad thing is the majority of the
endpoints that are going to have like
good impact for like file found or you
know if you're hitting the AWS metadata,
it's not going to be a 500. it's going
to be a 200. And so they actually I
don't know if he if he makes it clear in
this blog post if they had found this
before now and it triggered that in
their brain or since finding this they
went and found it other places. Did you
get a vibe of either way? I I think I
think they've noticed this behavior um
that we'll describe a little bit later
in a couple apps, you know, maybe one or
two in the past and then when it started
becoming a trend, they're like, "Okay,
what what's going on here?" And they
double clicked into it. Yes. And they do
speculate on what causes it, but there's
still not a definitive answer. So maybe
future research there would be kind of
interesting from our community. Um but
basically the way they um solved this is
they took they wrote a little bit of
Python code that that's shown here where
they each time that the redirect occurs
they increment the redirect response
code. So it's kind of interesting. So
their their server responds with a 301
then a 302 then a 303. I actually think
they skipped past 302 because they come
back to that for the final redirect. And
in their output here, it looks like they
start with 305, but may but that maybe
just they're showcasing that 305 and
above are what actually worked. That's
that's what it was. There was something
there was something weird with that
where, you know, they they wrote this
code that iterates across all of them to
try all the three, you know, the 300
status codes. And then somehow at the
end they found that the response that
was coming back was it was showing the
response for all of the the status
codes, so past 305. Um. Oh yeah, it was
like storing them up. Yep. Y exactly. So
you're seeing almost like a HTTP
pipelining sort of type response here
that was happening. Um and then so and
this is the line that kind of did it for
me on this one. It's like this drove us
nuts. Was there something special about
the 305 status code even though we
performed a redirect from 301 to 310?
Why did we only get the HTTP responses
from the status code 305 and above? Um
and they they went on to just kind of
going going through the rest of this. Uh
they went on to say that they don't
think that it was anything special about
305 or anything like that. It was just
the fact that there was some difference
in handling of the error conditions
between like the number of redirects
that were occurring. One is being
handled by lib curl and one's being
handled by the application layer and uh
that's what caused the mismatch. Yeah.
So if there any time there was more than
five. So basically, if instead of
iterating through them, you just did 301
five times and then switched to 307 or
something, it would start at 307.
Anything after the fifth attempt, it
would start or after the fourth attempt,
it would start um kind of logging is the
weird word to use there, but it would
kind of start logging it and then
respond with it. It would start handling
it in a different way. Yeah. And I'll
read this snippet from the the write up
so that you know there isn't any
confusion about what they said. Instead,
we believe that the application was
happy to follow a few direct redirects
and then failing on the JSON parsing.
Uh, and it was not happy about following
more than the max redirects configured
by lib curl. However, there was an error
state when it followed more than five
redirects not handled by lib curl, but
rather handled by the application
itself. This technique may sound obscure
to you, but it has now worked for us in
several situations where we would not
have been able to see the full HTTP
response for 200 okay requests, but
could see the full HTTP response for 500
status codes. So, I think that's the key
right there. The 500 status code, that's
your indicator that this is going to
actually that you should try this,
right? Yep. Yeah. Yeah. And I I mean
this may be a little bit of showing our
cards a little bit, but you and I were
talking before the podcast episode where
I honestly think that the community
needs some sort of tool, whether it's
built into Kaido or whether it's a
standalone tool where you give it like a
blind SSRF, like a request that will,
you know, um trigger a blind SSRF and
then because it's going to be on
different targets and whatnot, you
should maybe give it like some internal
IP or um internal host names for that
target because those are going to be
some of the checks or some of the tests
and basically make a blind SSRF
escalation app where it does like this
technique and lots of others like maybe
you know maybe it's looking for some
sort of specific DOS or some sort of
specific internal host like Jenkins dot
or Jira dot or something you know any
known things from that SSRF bible as I
sometimes allude to it the old asset
note post that has like all of the ways
to um increase the impact of SSRF maybe
you know somebody um includes a bunch of
different checks that could be done in
that case. Um, and if maybe if a list
isn't passed for known internet um,
based um, host names, then maybe it
takes a guess at someone's like
internal.root or whatever else. Yeah,
there definitely should be something
surrounding this. And I I just DM'd you
on on uh, Discord. There's this one surf
that asset not team released that sort
of uh hits different um you know sort of
candidates for for SSRF and tries to
enumerate you know hosts for within a
specific environment for it. Um, but
yeah, someone wants to just fork this
and and add more checks to it, right?
It's great. Yeah. Exactly. So, so I
think that this, you know, would be a
good base for that. And then we try some
of those escalation techniques from the
blind SRF. And the flow, just like you
said, should be like, all right, let me
just, you know, point this at some host,
you know, it could even be a hosted tool
that someone would use, right? Right.
Point it at some host. Um, and then like
essentially in automate, you know, just
give it like a numeric iterator and say,
"All right, give me a thousand, you
know, payloads or whatever." And then it
just hits it, hits it, hits it, hits it,
hits it. And then each time it says,
"All right, we're going to chain a
redirect 30 times. We're going to chain
a redirect 20 times. Exactly. You know,
301, 302, 303, you know, like yeah, this
like five and 30 threshold might have
might have might be the most common
misconfig, but I guarantee you there's
some where it's like greater than 10,
less than 50, whatever, you know, and
probably some where it's like it only
works for 302, some where it only works
for 307s, etc., etc., right? And there's
probably some permutations there where
there are ways to get full read SSRF
that people haven't found yet. Yeah,
totally, man. I'm excited for that.
Hopefully someone will build that out.
That'd be really cool. Yep. Um, all
right. I'm going to do this uh frame
busting one real quick. Yes, please do.
So, uh there was a something that hit
the intent to prototype list um that I
just kind of thought was interesting uh
and and kind of gives me a reason. Can
you refresh listeners what intent to
ship is? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Sure. So, um,
there are these Google groups that, uh,
the, um, I'm trying to think, the Blink
team, which is the the, uh, team behind
Chrome, uh, for a lot of the HTML and
and Java JavaScript, um, uh, you know,
progressions that happen, uh, new
features. And, um, one of the one of the
posts that were put in that Google group
was the intent to prototype, which is
that they're going to build this out.
They're going to build out this feature
um, for frame busting intervention. And
essentially this uh is some way for them
to prevent uh cross origin iframes from
navigating the top level browsing
context. And when I saw this I was like
crap that sucks cuz I like doing that.
Yeah. Um but I also thought you know
this this is something that maybe the
community might not be super aware of
because it is a little bit
counterintuitive that if you have an
iframe inside of a page and you control
that iframe then you can navigate the
top level page. um the just the fact by
the fact that you have you know that
you're I framed in on that page. This is
not true for sandboxed iframes without a
specific um I think allow top level
navigations um uh permission to be
attached to it but just a normal
straight iframe even if it's cross
origin you can navigate the top you know
top location right and you can set that
um so I just want wanted to remind the
listeners of that because uh it may be
going away soon and if you have exploits
that you need to kind of finish off that
utilize that then now would be the time
to do it. It's cool to see like there's
only 90 views on that right now on this
um request for comments or whatever.
Yeah. Yeah, man. You know, we we have a
little bot for the critical thinkers
that watches this and and tells us
whenever stuff is going to be released.
Um it's been very helpful in finding
stuff. Yeah. Great little like um just
preview of what you know either
potential future vulnerabilities or like
you said, old stuff that's going away
that's now going to be more secure,
which is just cool to stay on top of
even if there's nothing to be done about
it necessarily. Yeah. Yeah. It is a
little bit sad though. Every time like
something really like annoying comes
out, everybody in the critical thinkers
chat responds to it like no. Yeah. Like
oh no, they're do they're fixing this or
moving that. It's it's a pain. Yeah. But
it's also just the progression of
humanity moving forward. So let let me
add one more thing to that piece about
top uh like top level navigations um
from within the iframe. some you know it
is there are situations where that's
helpful but I want to remind you that if
you have a tab open and you opened up a
new website then you can always redirect
that tab unless coupe has severed the
connection. Mhm. So, that's something
that I kind of wanted to make sure the
listener understands is that uh you like
just because you're able to navigate the
top level page from within your iframe,
that doesn't mean that you're gaining
anything extra if you already have an
established uh frame reference from an
attacker controlled page. So, here's the
attacker controlled page. Here's the
page. You know, here's the little frame
reference right here or the um the
iframe. You know, if you already have a
relationship in these top two, then get
this doesn't, you know, have controlling
this iframe doesn't give you anything on
this top page. It's only when this
relationship is severed and you've just
got the act the window and then iframe
inside of it where okay, now I can use
top.loation to navigate the top level
frame when that results in something
impactful. What causes the connection to
other tab to be severed? Um, that that
can happen for a couple reasons, but the
most common one would be coupe, right?
which is a a cross origin opener policy
saying, "Okay, there can't be an opener
relationship between attacker.com and
google.com, right?" Um, and coupe is the
freaking bane of my existence, man. I
freaking hate stops all your bugs. Coupe
is like one of the worst things that for
an attacker that has ever happened to
browser security. So, um, yeah, and I've
done an episode on it, you know,
covering how to how to get around it as
as best you can, but sometimes there's
just not much you can do about it,
right? Sweet. Um, one other thing. Yeah,
actually I'll jump to the Hershey stuff
and then we can go then we can go down
to the liature next.
So, um, this is I posted in the critical
thinkers chat. Let me share my screen
and I will do my very best to articulate
this well to listeners. Yeah, this is a
hard one, dude. This is a hard one to
articulate. I think it is. Yeah, I I'm
honestly just going to hit the high
points and if people want to dig into
this, they can.
So, Horishi is a buddy of mine that is a
founder of a company called Southbridge
AI, and they're doing some cool stuff,
but it's all um in stealth right now,
and they can't talk about it. So, one
thing that he did that I thought was
really incredible, we'll actually talk
about a few different tools that he's
written that could be relevant to bug
hunters here in a second. But this
project that he did is extremely
relevant to bug hunters. So, basically,
he wanted to reverse engineer and fully
understand how cloud code works. And
cloud code is a tool from anthropic
that's like kind of similar to cursor
let you write code and stuff. I'm sure
most people have heard of it but it's
all offiscated minified JavaScript and
you know he wanted to understand it and
he's not like um like an offensive
security hacker or anything you know
he's a hacker in the developer sense and
so he wanted to understand this and he
was curious how far he could get with
current AI models. So, um, he wrote a
report, we'll link both these things,
about a breakdown all about how Cloud
Code works. And how he got there is
actually the second post he put out. I
think he was worried about them coming
at him for some sort of copyright
infringement or something, but he
eventually posted it. And that's the
that's the thing that I'm sharing right
now. And that's the thing that we'll
cover for those who are only listening
because there's a lot of really cool
takeaways. I actually thought that there
would be more kind of like hacker or
tool related takeaways where you know
it's like and as a result of doing this
I wrote this script that works really
well to do this but there's no scripts
in here. This is actually fully just AI
models and like the current AI chat apps
um basically processing and
understanding the JavaScript and then
like breaking it down in natural
language for humans to understand how it
works because that was his whole goal.
Mhm. So the the relevant piece for us as
you know hackers or virtual engineers
here is that what he does here is
essentially taking a an app right cursor
code and um or cloud code um and you
know breaking it down into this minified
JavaScript pieces and then getting the
AI to actually ingest this massive
amount of obfuscated minified code and
actually provide you with reasonable um
deductions about the architecture the
the flow of data through application and
that sort of thing and this is the
technique of how he did that. He cared
much more about how it works whereas we
would care much more about how to break
it or what the security of it is. So you
could imagine like this exact same blog
post being done by somebody in our
community where the questions they ask
of the app of the AI model is like hey
describe to me you know what are the
sources and syncs here for user input
what what are the potential areas for
security vulnerabilities are there any
hard-coded keys you know like these
types of questions and so like you know
even though he's doing this through the
through the frame of understanding how
it's built in a developer frame we would
definitely do this through a hacker
frame but one really key thing about
this that is like just so sweet
especially for you cuz I know you love
PC or GTFO and I love like getting into
the mind of other hackers is like um he
talks about all his failed attempts to
do it right just like we love seeing a
blog post it's like I tried this it
didn't work I tried this it didn't work
because you understand and you can begin
to understand how the mind of a top
level person works right top hacker in
our example but a top level AI engineer
in this example so um I think you know
uh just as a random aside here at the
top here's a video of him actually like
sped up at like, you know, 1,000% or
something of him writing this entire
blog post. I think I think in this day
and age, people are so skeptical that
everything's AI written. So, I think he
wanted to prove like, hey, this is me
manually typing out this like 5,000
words or whatever it is. That's crazy,
dude. That's amazing that he did that.
Yeah. So, he's got some really cool
architectures. The the takeaways here,
I'm just going to touch on a few of
them. It's way too much to cover in
full, but are the architecture that he
settled on for how he is using agents
and sub aents to break it down with a
lot of you of human input here. I'll say
this is not like a foolproof oneshot way
for um you know, one of our listeners to
just turn, you know, immediately take
this blog post and turn it into a system
that can then reverse engineer
JavaScript um minified obiscated
JavaScript. But I do think it gives a
lot of very strong tips and clues where
it could be that eventually. M um so he
um talks about it like kind of in two
different ways. My favorite is the
process notes. So if you jump down to
the process notes in here, he actually
talks about his like um kind of I think
this is maybe his raw paste of like what
he attempted. So the first thing he did
was he was trying to use Opus for
because it's so smart and break it into
20 different parts and have Opus analyze
the 20 different parts and kind of
communicate with itself and break it
down. But that's just too much disperate
context because as we all know in code
you can't just look at 120th of it and
understand what's going on because it's
often calling functions from other
places. It's it's inheriting classes
from other places. It's inheriting
libraries from other places. And so what
he ended up settling on and actually I
think this would give us a hard limit
because I think it was about 3 million
um tokens in context. So he was able to
get it into three chunks with Gemini 25
Pro instead of 20 chunks with Opus 4.
And so the the three chunks is much more
manageable to kind of sync across. But
you could imagine, let's say this app
was actually 20 million tokens. He would
have to use 20 chunks even for Gemini 25
Pro with the 1 million token context.
And again, it would probably be
unfeasible to um kind of break it down
in a way that was um or ingestable by
these AI models. And so maybe the hard
limit here is like you know 5 million
tokens of contact or something, but
cloud code is very big. And so my
takeaway here was for users is that most
apps you see today would probably be
usable by by this structure. Yeah. Okay.
So here's here's what I'm thinking for
this. Uh Joseph, here's here's what
we're going to do. You're going to go
through this and give give, you know,
describe the process that he had there
and I'm going to try to repeat back to
you what are the takeaways for hackers
that are architecting their own um you
know versions of this for hacking
purposes, right? The orchestration piece
with all the sub aents and that sort of
thing. So what I've got so far is that
um you know it's great it's very
tempting to try to use some of these
models that are just massive you know
big brain models but at the end of the
day um context is king in a lot of these
code related scenarios and because of
that we're forced to use Gemini which is
not that bad it's still ranked number
one on some of the rankings so yeah uh
but it also has a 1 million token
context window so that's what they're
using for actually the raw processing of
the data right that's right yeah for
these specific specifically. Yep. So,
the the Yeah, that's great. I like the
process here. He tried to just have it
used. So, whenever I say the sub agents,
we're talking about Gemini 25 Pro
because they're the only ones that can
hold enough context in them. But what he
eventually So, he tried just using sub
agents. So, Gemini 25 Pro sub agents to
process it. And then he kind of worked
as the as the orchestrator himself to
try to like copy and paste and
understand, you know, and kind of like
keep the thread going as he as he was
asking it deeper and deeper questions.
But what he what he converged on
eventually was actually some sort of
agent coordination with like a super
agent. Um, number one didn't work, so
I'm just going to kind of skip that. But
his sec his second and third attempt
worked much better. So he was using Opus
4 as basically an orchestrator agent.
I'm not familiar with Is that an
anthropic model? Is that Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. So, Sonnet and Opus are the two
bigger, you know, Sonnet's medium and
Opus is large and Haiku is the smallest
of the anthropic model. Sure. Okay. And
so, Opus 4 is like really smart. Um, and
particularly it's the best at writing
prompts. So, he he says that in here,
but that's a really great takeaway for
the listeners. If you ever like are
setting up an agentic system or you're
just about to, you know, use something
use AI to process your bug bounty report
or whatever and you want to write a good
system prompt, just pop in and ask Opus
for to write the prompt for you and you
give it the rough outline. It's it's so
good at writing prompts for other
models. That's that's what a what a
useful skill. That's great. Okay. Yeah,
exactly. So it's like a super prompt
writer. All right. So how does he apply
that here? Yeah. So he basically says um
I'm trying to understand this thing. So
this is the prompt orator agent. I've
got three sub agents working together to
understand each of the three parts
because it's too big to fit in one.
Here's their analysis and he kind of
copied and pasted in stuff from his
previous attempt to kind of get it going
on the right track. And then the
questions he wanted answered were like
so because this is a AI tool calling
thing. How are the tools called? How are
the tool outputs inserted back into the
context? What tools and functions exist
for managing the length of the context
etc etc right? Whereas if we were
building this, we would say something
like what are the sources in the sinks?
You know, for any potentially dangerous
sinks, what um you know, how many steps
does it have to flow through? Are there
any protections? Is there any Exactly.
What are the mitigating factors there?
And are they bypassable based on your
opinion or what that sort of thing,
right? And then um
is he put down here provide your
analysis as a long detailed
well-contextualized markdown document,
right? And then he would pass these kind
of he would then basically he would have
the orchestrator opus for the super
agent tell the sub agents hey these are
the answers we're trying to um get an or
these are the questions we're trying to
get an answer for. You kind of have
answered these three but you didn't
answer these other three and here's how
I ranked them in priority and you know
here's how you should look for those
answers. And so then they would
communicate back and forth. And so the
final um set of data like the final
answer from the super agent once it was
done kind of talking to the sub aents
the Gemini sub agents and they continued
to give context back then he used that
and that that um source document which
was like 300,000 tokens to then create
the report which you can read which is
that second link that I was talking
about which is like the full
understanding of the whole app. But when
it comes to um when it comes to actually
um understanding the architecture, this
is like a key piece I think for the
listeners. He wanted three main markdown
artifacts. The architecture of the
system in a high detail because then
that lets the AI models as they're
iterating know what to go look at,
right? It's almost like a checklist if
you think about it. Or when you're
coding with AI, it's like the plan it
makes first. If you if you don't have if
you don't ask it about what the
architecture is, it's probably going to
like not cover or not discuss lots of
things that are in there just by I don't
know by some sort of random mistake or
you know uh just overlooking it. Whereas
if you ask it what the full architecture
is including all of the classes or all
the function calls or all of the tabs or
all the pages in the app then now you
can have the AI make sure that it
answers questions about each of those
areas of the code. Dude, that is that is
a lot man. That is a freaking lot. Uh,
it's cool to see how he architected
this. And I'm wondering how and I don't
know that he covered it. I was just kind
of curs cursorally curs cursorally
cursory like like looking at a cursor
cursorally. I don't know. I don't know
what the word is for that. It's freaking
English, man. But I was just taking a
glance at the at the um at the write up
here trying to figure out how he glued
all this together. And I'm wondering if
he actually just like copied and pasted
the results from one chat to another.
But I feel like the best way to do that
would be lang chain right of like
getting all these together so that they
can uh like coordinate together or there
are a lot of agent frameworks these
days. I do think ling chain is probably
the most mature but it's going to have
the steepest learning curve. Mhm. Um I
would actually probably write from
scratch like you know these models are
pretty good at how at like doing like
traditional algorithms and so I would I
would probably just ask um you know Opus
4, Gemini 25 Pro or whatever to kind of
architect out a application where it has
to have agents that then return the
model just using the the REST APIs
directly
for for those for those uh for those
various um Yes. Yep. Yep. Exactly. Yeah.
I would just Yeah, because it's just so
it's like it's not that complex and and
I think the complexity of um learning a
new like basically hackers are just so
um adept with like scripts and are
hacky. Yeah, exactly. We're good with
scripts and we're good with REST APIs
and so it just makes so much more sense
to like just like be able to see how it
fully works without anything um hidden
in the background. Lang Chain has a
bunch of like system prompts and stuff
that are called whenever you're like
calling agents and stuff that very
likely are going to affect the output of
some of these tools in a way that you
might not expect and getting back to
them in the library code is kind of
annoying. I'm not great at like
debugging deep in like SDKs or library
code. And so I would imagine other
hackers are the same way, you know, like
they just want to see the full code and
the full prompt that's going to it. And
so I would actually just say like just
build it yourself in just a script and
it doesn't have to be anything super
fancy. Nice. Okay.
Yeah. Go ahead. No, you had a question.
I was just going to say like um so you
know takeaways so far you know Opus is
really good for writing prompts for for
other things. Um the the result of his
research here was that is that we the
best way to do this is to use a massive
context model to answer specific
questions generated by a more
intelligent orchestrator model, right?
And or orchestrator agent so to speak,
right? and then and then have that
bubble back up to the orchestrator and
then the orchestrator can actually ask
clarifying questions. Yes. Of each of
the the different um sub aents to get
the data it needs to make the correct
deductions. And that's how we are
effectively bubbling up that context
from the sub aents to the to the smart
model without losing you know without
having to use a massive amount of
context in the the the smarter model.
Yep. Yeah. Exactly. And I actually so
one thing that he emphasizes a few times
in this is that summarization is like
hard or impossible and I would have
never really thought about that because
I mean AI is pretty good at
summarization in my opinion but I think
when you're trying to understand a code
base it's just too lossy and so and so
you end up doing that but yeah I loved
the way that op that the way the super
agent the opus super agent was like
always asking Gemini 25 pro about um
like you said extra context. So here's
just like a really great sample example.
Whenever it's in communication with the
Gemini sub agents, it says, "Excellent
progress. Your analysis has revealed
these core insights. Uh but critical
implementation details are needed for
these things." And it's a list and it
says like, you know, high priority here,
high priority for this one, medium
priority for this one. And for anyone
just listening alone, um these sections
are just things that um that the models
that the super agent needed answers for
that the sub agents hadn't given it
answers for. And so it's asking for
clarification just like Justin just
said, it's asking clarifying questions.
Yeah, that's that's really cool because
then yeah, you're not really
surrendering the context at all because
that chat is still open where that
context is there and you can just pluck
out the data that you need from all of
these different pieces, right? And that
that's 1,000% exactly right because
those sub agents, not only do they have
like let's say they have 800,000 tokens
of context, but they have their own
internal monologue there about reasoning
through the pieces that it's already
bubbled up. So when the super agent
comes back and talks to it, it's still
in its own context without overflowing
the context of the super agent. Does
that make sense? Yeah, that makes sense.
That's pretty that's a smart way of
architecting it. Yeah. Yeah. It actually
makes me think a lot about like a
hacking team. Like I think this is
actually one core reason why people who
are collaborating with bug bounting and
hacking thrive and I and we never knew
it. It's because like when someone else
has a creative idea and then they ask
you about it, you actually still have
the context because you were the one
that found the initial lead or the
initial bug. And so then you're very
quickly able to be like, "Yeah, no, that
won't work because of this." So you're
tapping into their creativity, but
you're still keeping all of your
context. And this that's what happening
with the super agent. They're all just
LLMs, man. Oh my gosh. in some ways.
Yeah. Um, so anyways, down here, one
thing that I thought was really neat,
um, I showed this to you and you also
thought was pretty cool, he's written,
he's he's like, um, honestly, he reminds
me of, uh, is a guy named Arjun, the guy
who, um, no, Arjun was his tool. Yeah.
Yeah. Um,
dev something. Arjun, GitHub, Dev,
Python. Let's see. Yeah, I sumv. Yeah,
some dev. S O M D. Yeah. So Hershey kind
of reminds me of that where he has
written a bunch of different tools. One
is called Mandark and it's kind of a
Swiss Army knife which I don't you know
I'm very much of the Unix mindset
probably like you. I want to told to do
one thing really well but Mandar
specifically I'll click into it. One
thing that he uses it for and you even
show me you're not sharing it by the
way. Oh share this tab instead. Yeah. Um
so Mandark apparently can do a lot of
different things. It sounds like it's
just like an AI intern. I think he used
this before the models got better to
kind of make his models really good with
like good system prompts and other
things almost like fabric or LLM. But
anyways, one of the things that it can
do that he added features for is
basically printing out the codebase of a
bunch of files wrapped in XML tags so
that the LLM can see the beginning and
the end of the file as well as line
tagged numbers. So you can imagine like
in Vim or in your code editor when you
turn on line numbers you could see it on
the left. it includes those in the
output of the file. So then if you pass
it to an LM it can reference the line
number to the human or to the other sub
aents without there being like a
confusion there like oh on line 200
whenever this line was there because as
we know in code some line numbers are
replicated like you know they're
mentioned multiple times. Yeah that's
that's pretty rad dude. I I I think that
that's necessary for these AIs to be
able to communicate correctly because if
they don't, you know, if you're just
giving them those those pieces of code
as context, then, you know, they can
reference a specific line of code, but
where is that in the codebase, right? So
those, especially if you accompany it
with some sort of prompt that says, hey,
you know, make sure you provide a
specific file and line number, you know,
L, whatever for this. uh that'll
definitely be helpful in in uh in
getting it to provide more contextually
aware and specific responses. Yeah. And
another tool he uses later in this blog
post that you all will find super
useful. It's called Lumenus. Basically,
you can pass in it um any kind of text
transcript document your your bug bounty
notes or what have you. This is actually
I think probably be pretty cool for a
lot of bug hunters that have notes on a
specific program. Like let's say you're
an Amazon anchor hacker and you got a
bunch of notes like um you know maybe
Gret me does like Brandon he could just
throw all those in there and I'm stay on
this tab as I talk about this um but for
our listeners basically you know how
there are websites that have code
documentation where there's like a
really nice table of contents and you
can click around and there's like nice
headings and all that. It's like a
pertified website based on markdown.
That's kind of what this does. And so
you could imagine having these generates
that from your your just free form
notes. Is that what you're saying? Yep.
Yeah. So, it could generate it from one
of our conversations. If someone want to
take like a transcript of a CTBP episode
and throw it in there, it would
probably, you know, link to references.
It would probably, you know, show it in
nice bulleted list and like um a table
of contents that's clickable and stuff
like that. So, yeah, that's another tool
that he used in this whole process. Wow,
that's that's sick, man. Yeah. And go
hold on, go back to that last tab really
quick. Can you go back to that? Did it
say trending GitHub tool of the day?
GitHub trending number two repository of
the day. Dang, dude. That's kind of
crazy. Across all of GitHub. Uh, it's
not it's not now, but it was at some
point. Yeah, it was at one point. Wow.
Yeah, apparently you can. Wow. I've
never seen that before. That's pretty
sick. Yeah, it has 1.6K stars. Not bad.
Pretty popular repo. Um, all right. Did
you have any other takeaways from the
conducting smarter or conducting smarter
intelligences than me? I love that
title. That's great. Yeah, there was
just one thing that I wanted to cover. I
thought this was really nice. Um, in his
final report, he had basically some
model. I think you're on Lamentus again.
I'm not sure if you're trying to share
your Yeah. So, he had the report written
by Gemini 25 Pro simply because of the
context being greater than Opus 4 again,
but it was just kind of I think probably
too technical, too, too dense. And so,
he regenerated the report with Opus 4.
and he talks a lot about this strategy
in here. So um basically models will
often um go down the wrong path. They'll
start to describe something incorrectly
or they'll include a lot of output you
don't want or they'll be too repetitive
or they'll be in the wrong style you
want. And so he talks about it a lot in
this guide. Basically when you start
generating if you start seeing output
you don't like just stop it. Edit your
prompt. Regenerate it. Right? And so uh
you save those tokens you save your
time. You save your effort. I think too
many people are not doing that and
they're just unhappy with the output of
the AI and then they just move on to
something else, right? They don't use it
or they go run a different model when
really all they need to do is just tweak
the prompt a few different times and
just kind of regenerate it. And so he
talks about doing that here, but
anyways, what he ended up converging on
for his written report, and I'm not
going to read all of this, but there are
a few things that I thought in here were
were cool. He's like, we want this
report to be consumable by an audience
of deeply technical learners. Don't
reintroduce stuff. Stick close to
delivering value. Don't don't introduce
things or just talk about them like
actually you know deliver actual value.
The intent is to cover this this and
this um but be creative and you know
unique or whatever. And then this bottom
part it says expect a highle
intelligence from the reader. Don't talk
down to them. Think they're almost like
a senior engineer who's looking to learn
and implement. You don't need to tell
them that's good. You don't need to tell
them why but don't leave out any bit of
useful context or implementation
specifics that would be helpful. And so
I thought that was just like a really
cool thing just to throw in some prompts
because you know like there's so we've
all spent way too many hours reading
like filler text or just descriptions of
things when it's not being like
practical. It's almost what we do on
this podcast, right? Like our goal is to
bring really practical tips, not just
talk about the things, but talk about
what you can do with the things or what
you should invent to do with the things
so that you can improve the industry or
you can make more money or you can do
better in Bug Bounty. Right. So, right,
dude. And and I think looking at the
output of this thing, I'll I'll just
sort of share my screen as well. Um
looking at the output of this thing,
this is like a dream for a hacker who
was going to go hack this. Oh, you know,
like like there's just I mean look at
these sections. Dependencies, data
structures, control flow, tools,
architecture, novel components, file
editing, you know, like all all of these
are this is exactly what we would want.
This is like documentation for a tool
that is closed source
which is I mean what we do every single
day. So, it would be really amazing to
see this methodology, especially the
orchestration piece and that sort of
thing, um, copied into a tool that you
could just point at a JavaScript file, a
massive JavaScript file or a folder of
JavaScript files to have this um, to
have this happen. And I I I guess I
can't um I can't fail to mention that uh
what freaking XSS doctor did at Nomon
that was very similar to this which is
you know he took the web chunked pieces
of the uh JavaScript files from a given
web app and fed those into LLM and
provided summaries because those web
chunked pieces are smaller and already
compartmentalized you know for a
specific set of functionality. So they
should be you know um autonomous. They
should be not dependent on other pieces
of the code in in large way. Um and in
general in general I just think that
like um even if it's not 100% perfect,
right? Like Hishi Horishi is a little
bit of a perfectionist. So I think
that's why he wanted this to be like
very accurate with no hallucinations and
like very like oneshotty and very
whatever. But I think even doing stuff
like XSS doctor is a genius. I think
that if somebody's not as smart as
Rishier or XSS doctor, just like
throwing code you don't understand into
AI and being like, "Hey, tell me where
are some potential security issues? What
should I test here? What should I do?"
Can be really valuable even if you're
not going to build some huge verbo
system.
Yeah, absolutely, man. Um I'm I'm trying
to find real quickly here that piece. I
want to say it's multi-doc, but maybe
it's something else that he used for
that talk. So, I got to go get that
favored or something like that, but I'll
see if I can No, no, no. the not
multi-doc um uh JS collab. That's what
it's called. Here it is right here. I'll
I'll link it down in the description.
But that was that thing that I was
talking about where it uses Gemini to
like take all of the different pieces of
the JS and like provide the analysis for
them. So, it's a it's a great tool.
And then we had one last thing. This
weird Google logo liature, which I
cannot help but think this is going to
result in some bugs. Yeah, dude. This
one is super whack. Um, so this was just
this came I saw this a while back and it
just came up in conversation with me and
um, Reszo today, but the TLDDR of this
is that the font that was being used in
the URL bar for Chrome had uh, some
liatures defined in it that would allow
you to do spoofing. So, I'm sorry for
the listeners that are audio. This one's
a little bit more of a visual one, but
uh for the for you users that are are
watching on YouTube, you can see right
here that the URL bar has just a fancy
go ogle e, you know, net on it, right?
Um but if you look at the actual error
in the body, it says Google logol
liature.net was not found, right? Um and
so essentially what's happening here is
uh it this is actually requesting at the
DNS level a domain called Google
logoligure.net. net. Uh, but what's
being displayed in the URL bar is just
Google.net
uh with with a fancy style on it. So, it
allowed you to do really impactful URL
spoofing for Google.com, Google.net,
whatever um in the browser. So, very
very interesting um discovery I think.
Yeah. Yeah. We were talking about um and
you can actually still go replicate
this. So, it's kind of fun to play with.
You know, if you copy and paste one of
these special strings into Google search
on google.com. Yeah. Yeah. Let me let me
actually show you. What was it? O
Google. I had it in I have it in my
history right here. Yeah. Look at this.
Look. This is crazy. Look. Look at this.
I I select O Google logo liature right
here. And And look, it's the O not. It's
crazy, dude. So, it is crazy that this
still works on the Google search uh you
know bar right here. Um but the full
list of strings. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Um
hold on. So that's it's like G logo.
Yeah. So here's the um here is the list
right here. It's Google logo, G logo.
And then you've got, you know, E logo
liature, G logo, liature, L logo,
liature. The these individual characters
that are styled in the specific way that
Google wants them to be. Um and I'm
sorry, we didn't really go back and
explain font liatures, but that's kind
of what we do on this pod. Um much like
Opus model is not supposed to go back
and explain right you know so if you
need to Google what a font liature is go
Google what a font liature is um but
yeah so definitely a cool piece of
research here it put something on my
radar that I didn't have on my radar
before which is any place where spoofing
can be actually really security
impactful like a URL bar um you should
definitely be looking at the font that's
being used to render the text and check
for liatures that may result in a
mismatch between what's being displayed
and what's actually being held in the
value uh for that given uh you know
display of text. Yeah. And these
Chromium changes are open source. So if
you could find a bypass, it could result
in a vulnerability. Oh yeah, I'm glad
you brought that up, dude. The the fix
for this was kind of whack. So hold on,
let me let me share that, too. So here's
the code that was used to actually fix
this vulnerability. And instead of like
addressing the fact that this font has
liatures that they're using in their
their URL bar, they actually just
provide a deny list of like strings that
will result in these liatures occurring.
So um yeah, and then the code here is
just like domain.hostname.find
unsafe liature, you know, that that
needs to not exist. It needs to not be
in that in the string. Um or else it
won't resolve. So, it it seems like a
little bit of a band-aid patch to me,
sort of. Uh, but I'm sure there's a good
reason for the Google engineers to have
done it this way. Um, it just does not
protect us if there are additional font
liatures being pushed into the the font
that is being used in the URL bar for
Chrome. Um, so that could be a good area
to monitor if you're looking to get uh
you know, bounties in Google Chrome
itself. Um, and this what did this pay,
dude? How much was this? $15,000. 15 It
was $15,000 for this bug, which is
crazy. Um, so the team, the Google team
is definitely taking URL bar spoofing
very seriously. Yep.
Sweet. I think that's all that I've got
on our list. I think it's all you've got
on our list. Yeah, dude. Let's wrap it.
Good episode, man. Thanks, guys. Peace.
Peace. And that's a wrap on this episode
of Critical Thinking. Thanks so much for
watching to the end, y'all. If you want
more critical thinking content, uh, or
if you want to support the show, head
over to ctbb.show/isord. show/isord. You
can hop in the community. There's lots
of great highlevel hacking discussion
happening there on top of master
classes, hackalongs, exclusive content,
and a full-time hunters guild if you're
a full-time hunter. It's a great time,
trust me. All right, I'll see you there.